<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" ?>
		<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
			<channel>
				<title>Klassic Note Web Reports</title>
				<link>https://knwebreports.onrender.com/</link>
				<atom:link href="https://knwebreports.onrender.com/rss20.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
				<atom:link rel="hub" href="http://pubsubhubbub.appspot.com"/>
				<description>If it is worth taking Note, it will be a Klassic.</description>
				<language>en</language>
				<pubDate>Mon, 24 Jun 2024 22:06:08 +0800</pubDate>
				<item><title>The Entertainment News '24 Issue #25</title><description><![CDATA[Wow, all this season's Anime is back together once again! Well, for the last time apparently. Because this will be the start of the end of the Anime season with once again a record-breaking number of (maybe regretful) choices which could've taken another turn but hey, at least the best thing about this is <strike>all the friends we made along the way</strike> panties. *laughs* I still cannot forget about <strike>Noel-chan</strike> Moeshi's photobook dude, it's just too good it's making me catch colds left and right. *silence* Maybe I should go see a doctor. *laughs* Well, not to fret on that just yet, we got a season to conclude starting this week! And then maybe we'll talk about songs because those are rad too. *wink*<blockquote class="tr_bq anime" id="TenshiTsuki12"> <div style="text-align: center;"> <span clas]]></description><link>https://knwebreports.onrender.com/posts/2024/06/the-entertainment-news-24-issue-25.html</link><pubDate>Sun, 23 Jun 2024 22:00:00 +0800</pubDate></item> <item><title>The Entertainment News '24 Issue #24</title><description><![CDATA[Oh, the planets have aligned, we are at issue number 24 of the year 24- Who cares haha let's move on. Damn, was this a great weekend so far considering it's one day longer just so that I can j- So that I can review the package of the month which of course, includes the one and only Moeshi photobook which I will consider her best since I never bought one of hers before. *giggles* Not in the 5 years I knew of her. Thanks though, this is so great apart from the fact that I got it signed, I wonder why I keep thinking of <a href="https://myanimelist.net/character/238861/Noeru_Izumi" target="_blank" >Noel-chan</a >&nbsp;from Anime "Tenshi Tsuki" and her underwear all this time.*silence* Moving on, offloading *wink* my load *wink* and instead transferring that energy to talk about Anime and music this week! Oh boy, do we have more things going on than ever before- I]]></description><link>https://knwebreports.onrender.com/posts/2024/06/the-entertainment-news-24-issue-24.html</link><pubDate>Sun, 16 Jun 2024 22:15:00 +0800</pubDate></item> <item><title>The Twenty-Fourth Book Worth of Photos: Motif Overflowing, Like a Work of Art</title><description><![CDATA[I was thinking of using Sleeping Beauty to fit the theme after I've seen the book but probably not since this can hardly make me take a nap now HAHA we got sheep here though so maybe...? Sorry for not being serious about this though so I just went overboard with the title here hehe she will get my sense of humour. This came in on time for the weekend or maybe not I had to take this from the post office lol, but I gotta say this is all worth it because I did not realize that I have legit waited FIVE YEAR for this, ever since I knew of this woman back in 2019. Without further ado, let's talk about how this all fell into place, shall we?<table align="center" cellpadding="0" cellspacing="0" class="tr-caption-container" style="margin-left: auto; margin-right: auto;"> <tbody> <tr> <td style="text-align:]]></description><link>https://knwebreports.onrender.com/posts/2024/06/the-twenty-fourth-book-worth-of-photos.html</link><pubDate>Sat, 15 Jun 2024 18:30:00 +0800</pubDate></item> <item><title>The Welfare Package June 2024: The Pre-Summer Special!!!</title><description><![CDATA[Well I was just watching my <a href="https://jisho.org/search/imouto" target="_blank">imouto</a> <a href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=dD-qC_7Oc2U" target="_blank" >Natsukawa Shiina stream video games</a > and talking about her revival Pre-2nd album live (while forgetting to stop 10 minutes after <a href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=jIk19VLJx4c" target="_blank" >the extra paid segment</a > which was free because of niconico is down since this week for *prays* who knows how long) so taking inspiration from that for the title. You're welcome, Nan. *dabs* ANYWAYS, summer is already here why would I write like it hasn't come yet considering this place is an oven since two months ago lol, STILL could not compare to the last time I was this hype which was like, last month. *giggles* Nonetheless, the monthly motivation is here and despite this missing the delivery at home WITH TWO PEOPLE AROUND *ugh*, hey at l]]></description><link>https://knwebreports.onrender.com/posts/2024/06/the-welfare-package-june-2024-pre.html</link><pubDate>Fri, 14 Jun 2024 23:15:00 +0800</pubDate></item> <item><title>The Entertainment News '24 Issue #23</title><description><![CDATA[Hey good news: The next season of The Fanfiction series will start next month to coincide with the site migration! And this time around, I will move out of the comfort zone. No, I meant this blog. We are still into the tales of girls I like. *giggles* Bad news is man, I am SO STOKED stoked at the next season of my Fanfiction series since like, last month haha yeah I planned it all, I'm just gyrating here right now ready to write this every Saturday as usual in a couple of weeks, I have been revising the stories I wrote over the past year! So yeah, if you don't mind you can read it back, I maaaaay have tweaked some of them to not sound like I want to bang my married cousin or- Speaking of marriage, heck, I'm just glad that people like Fuchigami Mai and happy birthday Tsuda Minami in their 30s are finding their true love. Gives me hope that I'll find mine at some point *prays* once I decide to c]]></description><link>https://knwebreports.onrender.com/posts/2024/06/the-entertainment-news-24-issue-23.html</link><pubDate>Sun, 09 Jun 2024 22:15:00 +0800</pubDate></item> <item><title>The Entertainment News '24 Issue #22</title><description><![CDATA[Damn, I was thinking of migrating the blog so much I was dreaming about taking a math exam in university without any studying?? Where's my morning coffee at? *looks at desk* Oh there it is, thank goodness. *giggles* Hey welcome back. As much as I want to talk about new fanfiction, and as much as I want to review the next package already and how much I want confirm that I got a signed Moeshi photobook *giggles* AND as much as I am desperate to come up with a more rounded solution into moving OUT of Blogger? It's not happening, dudes, not the last one, but I do aim to make it much simpler like the one at GitHub and recently on Render. Not like the others are going to happen anytime soon too, so we shall see how it goes. I'm still moving to a new site though, that's for sure. So, let's forget those right now and get in just on time for new music and Anime...? Hey, Anime "SasaKoi", you there?&nbsp]]></description><link>https://knwebreports.onrender.com/posts/2024/06/the-entertainment-news-24-issue-22.html</link><pubDate>Sun, 02 Jun 2024 22:08:00 +0800</pubDate></item> <item><title>The Entertainment News '24 Issue #21</title><description><![CDATA[Weekends are short, aren't they? Short enough for me to not be able to do more despite spending the past day and a half to do up my GitHub site, scan more of them photos of Kido Ibuki so I can *fap fap fap* haha that beige swimsuit is too much for my virgin heart, and take a break- I didn't do the last one though, there was no time for a nap. And that's the problem. *laughs* The DOAXVV half anniversary gacha rolls are making it up for it though haha Monica-chan~!!!! *giggles* Oh well, we are not getting the breaks today also because it takes a lot of effort to do this and I don't know how to streamline this despite the anniversary of the blog coming soon and Blogger is breaking by the way it can't even do links properly now... So let's not think too much and talk more of Anime and music!!<!--SECTION BREAK--><blockquote]]></description><link>https://knwebreports.onrender.com/posts/2024/05/the-entertainment-news-24-issue-21.html</link><pubDate>Sun, 26 May 2024 22:22:00 +0800</pubDate></item> <item><title>The Entertainment News '24 Issue #20</title><description><![CDATA[Oh damn, since I practically tried to do nothing yesterday since I have been for the past few days *wink* don't ask, and I technically want to catch the live singing event of Rikachimalu (yes, not MaiMai), so we better clear our weekly watchlist as much as possible! Yeah, both events so I will watch some in the morning before the noon event haha this is so unprecedented I can't even. If you aren't keen on all of this, at least catch up on the bromide photo stack I just got recently with the new package, and tell me all that is not enough because I wish I could sync with one of the later ones which will also have way more. Well, at least you and I know what's coming up in next month's package it's MOESHI PHOTOBOOK LETS GO-So yeah, let's Anime and music!<!--SECTION BREAK--><blockquote class="tr_bq anime" id="TenshiTsuki0]]></description><link>https://knwebreports.onrender.com/posts/2024/05/the-entertainment-news-24-issue-20.html</link><pubDate>Sun, 19 May 2024 22:11:00 +0800</pubDate></item> <item><title>The Welfare Package May 2024: The Bromide Photos Takeover</title><description><![CDATA[Well, almost. It would have been a takeover if the Hondo Kaede x Naganawa Maria ones were to arrive at the same time too MUAHAHAHAHAHA thank goodness we are still setting a record here though. You'll get it in a bit. *giggles*Also, a package with so many fanclub stuff but no Minase Inori newsletter in it?WHAT??? Haha welcome back for another series of this... damn has it already been5 years since I spent more money in Japan than in my home country so much sothey have to tax me for financing a country whose economy is dwindling, dude??*laughs* Alright jokes aside though, I'm still hyped as I should be coming up inthis post here, because guess what, this time around to compensate for the lackthereof the previous time, this time around is basically a bromide photoshowcase!! Almost, because we have to pick up on the fanclub stuff I missed lastmonth too and that's why this came in on a slightly different schedule than*wink* a certain photobook]]></description><link>https://knwebreports.onrender.com/posts/2024/05/the-welfare-package-may-2024-bromide.html</link><pubDate>Fri, 17 May 2024 22:30:00 +0800</pubDate></item> <item><title>The Entertainment News '24 Issue #19</title><description><![CDATA[I'm already having dreams of not being able to watch all the Anime weekly on Sundays. *sob* Maybe I just need my coffee fix. *looks at table* Got it! *laughs* So yeah, I think I'm okay now, need to monitor myself as usual and probably my future ahead of me this year which isn't the worst thing by comparison, but seeing how the world out there is somewhat on fire despite not having a pandemic roaming the lands (and seas), I wonder how I can even survive till next year to do most of my tech upgrades. *silence* We will deal with that in due time.Meanwhile! *giggles* We got Anime and music to talk about, so let's!<!--SECTION BREAK--><blockquote class="tr_bq anime" id="TenshiTsuki06"> <div style="text-align: center;"> <span class="head-prefix"><b>アニメ</b></span >&nbsp;<span style="font-size: large;" >One Room, Hi]]></description><link>https://knwebreports.onrender.com/posts/2024/05/the-entertainment-news-24-issue-19.html</link><pubDate>Sun, 12 May 2024 22:05:00 +0800</pubDate></item> <item><title>The Entertainment News '24 Issue #18</title><description><![CDATA[Wow did I make this week the best and worst of the year yet. *laughs* Not only did I write a story with women I adore every day of the weekday be sure to check them out and you're welcome, I also had a cold drink in the middle of the week to celebrate the hot weather so I can have diarrhoea for the rest of the week which is still recovering as of now. *silence* I need better life advice haha But yeah, the hot weather has somewhat subsided where I live, and the package is coming in together rather nicely, so yeah that's a plus. Also a plus is me spending the weekend fixing up the blog again, this time adding in 2017 entertainment news to the sitemap (not in Blogger), so yeah, in case you missed <a href="https://myanimelist.net/anime/34934/Koi_to_Uso" target="_blank" >Anime "Koi to Uso"</a > or <a href="https://myanimelist.net/anime/32949/Kuzu_no_Honkai" target="_blank" >"Kuzu no Honkai"</a > lmao yes I reject]]></description><link>https://knwebreports.onrender.com/posts/2024/05/the-entertainment-news-24-issue-18.html</link><pubDate>Sun, 05 May 2024 22:13:00 +0800</pubDate></item> <item><title>The Fanfiction 20240503</title><description><![CDATA[Man, I didn't actually plan for this to be written the next day of whatever music video I watched last night, but with whatever that I saw on it that is more than just creepy lol, maybe writing this story afterwards is better than whatever is imprinted at the back of my brain. *giggles* Yes, I am talking about <a href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=vPtfcPi70Gs" target="_blank" >Asakura Momo's new music video</a > which kind of makes sense at this point for the song title, but damn if you need to freak out about Mocho loving you some way... Uh, maybe this one I'm ending the season with will cheer you up! Haha my impression of her is this, not going to let whatever that got me last night scar me forever lmao <div class="separator" style="clear: both; text-align: center;"> <img alt="Asakura Momo in a orange sweater hugging on to]]></description><link>https://knwebreports.onrender.com/posts/2024/05/the-fanfiction-20240503.html</link><pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 11:00:00 +0800</pubDate></item> <item><title>The Fanfiction 20240502</title><description><![CDATA[We're still moving on strong so far and not like my health condition is any indication, but hey, maybe this will heal me up...? *laughs* Sorry for saying that this is the story I'm most excited for the week after what we did with Ten-chan for last month (hehe) but yeah, it just got me more hyped the more I think about it. In fiction, yes, this is still not real life. This will also introduce us to a new character in the most stereotypical way possible and that's why I watch livestream duos and such, as your friend's friend. You will get what I mean in a moment. LET'S GO HIDE!! *giggles*<div class="separator" style="clear: both; text-align: center;"> <img alt="Ueda Reina in a white dress hiding behind white curtains putting her hands against the white window" border="0" data-original-height="512" data-original-width="359" height="200"]]></description><link>https://knwebreports.onrender.com/posts/2024/05/the-fanfiction-20240502.html</link><pubDate>Thu, 02 May 2024 11:00:00 +0800</pubDate></item> <item><title>The Fanfiction 20240501</title><description><![CDATA[Well, we're halfway through the week already, how are you guys doing? It's great for me because I AM FREE UNTIL NEXT WEEK!!! Living the true holiday spirit this year once again- That tinnitus on my left ear though... *laughs* This time around, I'm featuring someone we know all too well about but I've hardly written about her, so let's do this story the same impression I have of her now! Then again I wonder if I'm that nice to help people out...Fictional me, right? Then I guess I am haha *wink*<div class="separator" style="clear: both; text-align: center;"> <img alt="Uesaka Sumire dressed in a white top with a dark blue jacket and yellow skirt, pouting and carrying a large plastic box with both hands" border="0" data-original-height="512" data-original-width="356" height="200" src="https://www]]></description><link>https://knwebreports.onrender.com/posts/2024/05/the-fanfiction-20240501.html</link><pubDate>Wed, 01 May 2024 11:00:00 +0800</pubDate></item> <item><title>The Fanfiction 20240430</title><description><![CDATA[Since I will be halfway done with the work week by the time you have seen this noon time published week-long special, you know what's the best way to unwind after a day of hard work? YouTube- Uh, I mean, hanging out at a bar! Hey, it may be lonesome juice bar that you don't even drink, me, you are neither of those so thank goodness there is fictional me so I can write about this next story! I've always wanted a drinking buddy, so this should set things up. Maybe. We can be friends. *giggles*... HEY GOD OF GLASS&nbsp;<a href="https://myanimelist.net/character/3741/Ryuu_Sasakura" target="_blank" >SASAKURA RYUU</a > HELP ME OUT ON THIS!! *laughs*<div class="separator" style="clear: both; text-align: center;"> <img alt="Aizawa Saya dressed in a gray dress with a black sleeved top, holding o]]></description><link>https://knwebreports.onrender.com/posts/2024/04/the-fanfiction-20240430.html</link><pubDate>Tue, 30 Apr 2024 11:00:00 +0800</pubDate></item> <item><title>The Fanfiction 20240429</title><description><![CDATA[Well, we're in Japan's Golden Week... week now, so I have planned something special!! To celebrate what is almost a year or me writing stories of fictional me interacting with women which itself should be considered a miracle (lol), I will have fresh stories every single day until Friday! We are starting of with... well all stories have a beginning and this one is too even for fictional me so...Shall we begin?<div class="separator" style="clear: both; text-align: center;"> <img alt="Kitou Akari dressed in a black blouse and pink coat, standing by a tree in the background" border="0" data-original-height="357" data-original-width="512" height="139" src="https://www.suruga-ya.jp/database/pics_light/game/gl367784.jpg" title="Kitou Akari" width="200" /><blockquote>]]></description><link>https://knwebreports.onrender.com/posts/2024/04/the-fanfiction-20240429.html</link><pubDate>Mon, 29 Apr 2024 11:00:00 +0800</pubDate></item> <item><title>The Entertainment News '24 Issue #17</title><description><![CDATA[Yeah, I did not do the round-up I said I would do for the Fanfiction series, I'm sorry. This is because I was trying to test the blog migration thing I've been trying out for so long, gave up halfway for trying to fix all the scripts and files that are making this more of a mess to deploy separately to another service, ended up making me do other stuff on my GitHub pages which made me even more pissed fixing the older versions I wish I could just spend more time to redo them.*silence* Hey, I promise you I was having fun haha I know it doesn't sound like it but that's programmer life. *giggles* Also Japan online shopping life I spent WAY too much money on bromides this month alone, we shall collate them next month when they arrive. You'll see. *giggles* And since I didn't watch any Anime on a Saturday, I shall pay the price and rush all of them on a Sunday! The onl]]></description><link>https://knwebreports.onrender.com/posts/2024/04/the-entertainment-news-24-issue-17.html</link><pubDate>Sun, 28 Apr 2024 22:12:00 +0800</pubDate></item> <item><title>The Entertainment News '24 Issue #16</title><description><![CDATA[Looks like this might be my Anime list for the season! We shall see, <a href="https://myanimelist.net/anime/54233/Sasayaku_You_ni_Koi_wo_Utau" target="_blank" >Anime "SasaKoi"</a > hasn't really gotten me yet even though it has gotten Himari-chan. *laughs* As such, I will be doing this season of shows throughout the weekend (sadly), and this still depends on whether I can get enough break from my new assignment at work: It'll take no time for me to get to work because the location is different, but whether that is closer to Hell or not is hard to say. Will report if I consider skipping doing this weekly post entirely if I have to. *laughs* Jokes aside, I still need motivation despite being under the weather as always lol, so yeah, maybe putting the angel to start instead of ending it might be a good idea after all haha ah hey</]]></description><link>https://knwebreports.onrender.com/posts/2024/04/the-entertainment-news-24-issue-16.html</link><pubDate>Sun, 21 Apr 2024 22:10:00 +0800</pubDate></item> <item><title>The Fanfiction 20240420</title><description><![CDATA[ANOTHER STORY FEATURING TEN-CHAN AGAIN!?? Alright, we made a joke about this already. *giggles* This is also the last of them anyways, but not in plot because we are continuing the story from last week! Hell yeah I told you I can do sequels no one is going to stop me. *wink* I also know today is weed day but we are not talking about that haha, because if dear Amamiya Sora is my weed, I will die from drug addiction. *laughs* Ah hey, what can I say, I want to- Why can't I say it? Yo, stop censoring me I want to sleep with- HUH?? *laughs* Yeah, imagine censoring myself- Wait. What if this is fictional me censoring real me? Oh damn, did I manifest something bad that will ensure my virginity? Well, at least this story will. *giggles* Let us clear our mind of reality and step into the conclusion for this season's world of fiction!! LET'S GO OUT WITH A BANG-<]]></description><link>https://knwebreports.onrender.com/posts/2024/04/the-fanfiction-20240420.html</link><pubDate>Sat, 20 Apr 2024 16:20:00 +0800</pubDate></item> <item><title>The Entertainment News '24 Issue #15</title><description><![CDATA[I'm going to start this one early on a Saturday because we have A LOT to cover this week. For this week is likely the decision checkpoint for all the new shows that are appearing for the new season specifically on Anime, and we are going to WATCH THEM ALL- Okay not all of them, I do have my plans on what I want and not want to watch this season, so it's just a matter of them living up to my expectations. I can't reject sequels anyways so they don't count. *laughs* Oh and order doesn't matter this week too because I am still figuring out what will make me want to do this every week first for or the next 3 months so *shrugs* Music this week has also been great too, so we will talk about those after we deal with my weekend naps being burnt on watching animated girls and dudes...? Uh oh haha why are there so many of them though<br]]></description><link>https://knwebreports.onrender.com/posts/2024/04/the-entertainment-news-24-issue-15.html</link><pubDate>Sun, 14 Apr 2024 22:08:00 +0800</pubDate></item> <item><title>The Fanfiction 20240413</title><description><![CDATA[Wha~t!! Another story featuring Ten-chan again?? Yes, it has come back once again because as I said, this is just compensating for only mentioning her the one time, and I'm here to make it up to her. Not her personally, she has to be in my fiction in order to interact with fictional me.*sigh* Now that we let the cat out of the bag, maybe we just start with extrapolating my... invisible role in the eyes of my stepsister's career: Being the sort of a substitute manager or errand boy I guess at her beck and call? So yeah, basically when Nan-chan says go there, I go there. She says I go with Ten-chan, I go with Ten-chan...!? OKAY THEN LET'S GO TO SOMEWHERE FAR AWAY!! *giggles* Ah hey<div class="separator" style="clear: both; text-align: center;"> <img alt="Amamiya Sora barefeet wearing a dark blue blouse, translucent sl]]></description><link>https://knwebreports.onrender.com/posts/2024/04/the-fanfiction-20240413.html</link><pubDate>Sat, 13 Apr 2024 19:39:00 +0800</pubDate></item> <item><title></title><description><![CDATA[<b>To work is for passion, but passion is not for work.</b><br>It's an irony isn't it? People keep saying out there that you should have passion on the work you do, but knowing that isn't enough especially when you have your livelihood ie. your salary on the line. And that is assuming most of us in the workforce, if you are a freelancer or even a business owner you would also have the passion, but the purpose of that would be different. And that just brings us back to why when we do anything with a passion often associated as a known hobby, we don't do it for the sake of earning money. They just can't simply coexist even in the ones that supposedly can, like illustrators. There will be that line, and I just hate that it exists.<br>The solution? I hope that you are passionate in more than one thing that can put money on the dining table.]]></description><link>https://knwebreports.onrender.com/posts/2024/04/to-work-is-for-passion-but-passion-is.html</link><pubDate>Fri, 12 Apr 2024 19:45:00 +0800</pubDate></item> <item><title>The Twenty-Third Book Worth of Photos: My Idol Cannot Be This Cute</title><description><![CDATA[I just made this title up haha I had no idea what to use to describe this adorable piece of- Shout out to <a href="https://myanimelist.net/anime/8769/Ore_no_Imouto_ga_Konnani_Kawaii_Wake_ga_Nai" target="_blank" >Anime "OreImo"</a > for the inspiration haha I guess mine is called "Ore<a href="https://jisho.org/search/aidoru" target="_blank" >Idol</a >" hehe <i>nice</i>. And to this, I should apologize beforehand because SORRY TO KEEP YOU WAITING haha yes including you, me, for having to wait TWO DAMN WEEKS just to get more of MaiMai because I had to wait for the rest of the free fanclub stuff to arrive so I can save some money on international shipping- Hey MaiMai you coming up with a fanclub subscription soon with monthly wallpapers? *giggles* Well, I guess she is already making me pay monthly for her livestreams so... Anyways I lose lol, and I formally welcome my birth]]></description><link>https://knwebreports.onrender.com/posts/2024/04/the-twenty-third-book-worth-of-photos.html</link><pubDate>Fri, 12 Apr 2024 19:31:00 +0800</pubDate></item> <item><title>The Klassic Note Review 2024.04</title><description><![CDATA[I promised I will be back with another CD review after last month we are just on delay for a month just like how Japanese magazines are with their edition naming, but <strike>this is</strike> we are on a roll right now with these music reviews!! Ah hey, what can I say, I have not been generous but then again the good releases have been increasing, so screw you guys RyokuShaka and Creepy Nuts for not making it into the shelf (lol), and let's talk about some veteran who really deserves some mentioning about like, years since the last time I did this for her! It's such a wild turn, I'm pretty sure I was still rejecting her songs a month ago haha<blockquote class="tr_bq music" id="miwaSoredemoTada"> <div style="text-align: center;"> <span class="head-prefix"><b>音楽</b></span >&nbsp;<span style="font-size: large;">The Klassic Note Review</span> </blockquote><blockquote]]></description><link>https://knwebreports.onrender.com/posts/2024/04/the-klassic-note-review-202404.html</link><pubDate>Thu, 11 Apr 2024 20:13:00 +0800</pubDate></item> <item><title>The Welfare Package April 2024: Renewing Vows</title><description><![CDATA[No, not wedding vows. I'm still single, remember? Yes, even fictional me. *laughs* If this is not the latest version of "<a href="https://jisho.org/search/keikakudoori" target="_blank" >all according to plan</a >" I can't make this orchestration any better. *giggles* Okay maybe I missed the newsletter which just dropped by the forwarding service this morning but heck, that was already calculated. But otherwise, you would be pleased to hear that the monthly package has dropped by! And I could not be more hyped to talk about them, mainly because as annoying as this is, I just updated my... simping(?) to some fanclubs, renewing the "vows" I did for each year on my birthday month and maaaaybe it was a bad idea to do it on the final day of <strike>Febriary</strike> February and let them charge me again once the month ticks over and/or make the subscription end a month earlier for the yearly plans.<]]></description><link>https://knwebreports.onrender.com/posts/2024/04/the-welfare-package-april-2024-renewing.html</link><pubDate>Thu, 11 Apr 2024 15:15:00 +0800</pubDate></item> <item><title>The Entertainment News '24 Issue #14</title><description><![CDATA[Wow, how did I end up on the same state as I were two weeks ago, I don't even know. *silence* Oh I meant physically, mentally I'm already ruined once I reached 30 so if I'm not feeling well this is quite normal. *laughs* Also normal and totally expected, is the new season of Anime!! Yeah let's not talk about how I'm coughing again I rather be coughing up reviews of new shows I am interested in to see if I want to watch any of them other than the sequels which will already fuel the next three months of my weekends. *giggles* We shall see, me, we shall see. Hey, at least we have some time to give these, huh? I will try this time around- It's the new year, we gotta try somehow.&nbsp; Anime will compensate for the lack of music this week and likely prep us for the months ahead because I have to give the theme songs haha, in this new season start of stuff I talk about every week! I need a better sl]]></description><link>https://knwebreports.onrender.com/posts/2024/04/the-entertainment-news-24-issue-14.html</link><pubDate>Sun, 07 Apr 2024 22:07:00 +0800</pubDate></item> <item><title>The Fanfiction 20240406</title><description><![CDATA[Well, I hear this could be <a href="https://tenki.jp/sakura/" target="_blank" >the best weekend for cherry blossom season in Tokyo</a > so I better do this seasonal story up before it dies out in about two days lol It might be a good day for an outing today, because damn did I botch up a lot of stuff just being at home. Breakfast home delivery was super screwed for some reason I shall not iterate, and I guess we still haven't planned for the mom's birthday dinner for tonight. *silence* Well I'll think of something while trying to curb my anger, because seriously, how am I going to be mad when I spent so much time just thinking of how to write this month's stories featuring fictional me? Shout out to half a year ago when I wanted to write more of this woman, and here we are! Don't worry, me, you can do perfection over here this isn't real life she is totally up your alley and]]></description><link>https://knwebreports.onrender.com/posts/2024/04/the-fanfiction-20240406.html</link><pubDate>Sat, 06 Apr 2024 14:00:00 +0800</pubDate></item> <item><title></title><description><![CDATA[<b>People don't just simply change their character accordingly. They typically suppress their character by keeping up a front and/or be uncomfortable around people who tell them what to be.</b><br>And then they just change their environment by leaving. Feels familiar yet?<br>Well, for me though, I just stay and ignore everything which is also rather unprofessional and unexpected as a human in society, you then realize what I just wrote is basically an irony in itself because that is also what will change you, unwillingly. So yeah, what defines us again? I don't think I will ever get this part about life.<br><br>]]></description><link>https://knwebreports.onrender.com/posts/2024/04/people-dont-just-simply-change-their.html</link><pubDate>Tue, 02 Apr 2024 18:17:00 +0800</pubDate></item> <item><title>The Entertainment News '24 Issue #13</title><description><![CDATA[Wow, was this another long weekend. *giggles* Hey, I can use more of those. Between making money and just being in front of my PC all day fixing up blog stuff (I didn't change anything here, just cleaning up code behind), I'm just glad I still have the sanity to write some fanfic here and there, oh boy is next month and likely the concluding month for the season going to be great. *laughs* Ah hey, they don't know yet, me. Don't tease the readers. *giggles* Anyways, new season of Anime incoming which also means I better enjoy the little break from music before they throw me a buttload of new theme songs which have no physical release *oof* haha, but before all that, let us wrap stuff up.<!--SECTION BREAK--><blockquote class="tr_bq anime" id="KanaTen12"> <div style="text-align: center;"> <span class="head-prefix"><b>ア]]></description><link>https://knwebreports.onrender.com/posts/2024/03/the-entertainment-news-24-issue-13.html</link><pubDate>Sun, 31 Mar 2024 22:05:00 +0800</pubDate></item> <item><title>The Fanfiction 20240329</title><description><![CDATA[You know it's a good Friday when... you look at the calendar today and it says "Good Friday" haha so yeah, doing this slightly earlier today for the occasion. Also for the occasion, let me take this chance to say <a href="https://x.com/3rdMR_staff/status/1773364439212839227?s=20" target="_blank" >happy birthday to Miyazawa Koharu</a >, arguably the best member in MusicRay'n 3rd Generation (still no group name yet lol), just a beauty in general and if have not heard of her saying "<a href="https://jisho.org/search/yada" target="_blank" >yada</a > yada" you <i>need</i> to watch the weekly video livestream(?) series on Tuesdays (whenever she is featured) to hear her say it. She's 25 though. *laughs* We got more lore to talk about and it isn't about real life just because I'm single haha *sob*, this time we shall talk about someone who is also young! Well, anything below]]></description><link>https://knwebreports.onrender.com/posts/2024/03/the-fanfiction-20240329.html</link><pubDate>Fri, 29 Mar 2024 13:23:00 +0800</pubDate></item> <item><title></title><description><![CDATA[<b>Learn to give the same reactions towards things that went well and when they aren't, whatever those reactions are.</b><br>It might be ridiculous to like, appreciate things when they go right, or even not have any reaction when things go wrong. It's understandable to have to react to stuff nowadays, that's how the Internet works anyways. But the bias towards criticism is really going so much sideways compared to the praise given out there... Maybe it's our problem for not reacting appropriately to the occasion, is all I can imagine how this world works, to be frank.<br>And it's not because I'm old I have been old since I graduated elementary school lol]]></description><link>https://knwebreports.onrender.com/posts/2024/03/learn-to-give-same-reactions-towards.html</link><pubDate>Thu, 28 Mar 2024 18:25:00 +0800</pubDate></item> <item><title>The Entertainment News '24 Issue #12</title><description><![CDATA[*yawns* Haha must be rough taking half the week off, yes? Well, not purely intentional, but purely coincidental it was, and I'm glad I get to take my week deserved break for the month (lol), though I guess there's next week too but my mental health is already affecting my physical health like we all do so I think I shall use this excuse to live my life from now on. *laughs**sigh* It's understandable if you need to rewrite this intro lol me then again maybe consider rewriting the fanfic for the week also while you're at it? Why are the stories recently of fictional me offending women? Haha *dabs* Anyways, Anime and music! I just want to distract myself from whatever sadness might be happening to any of them, to be honest. Then again me, didn't you want to watch <a href="https://myanimelist.net/anime/53747/Kimi_no_Iro" target="_blank"]]></description><link>https://knwebreports.onrender.com/posts/2024/03/the-entertainment-news-24-issue-12.html</link><pubDate>Sun, 24 Mar 2024 22:05:00 +0800</pubDate></item> <item><title>The Fanfiction 20240323</title><description><![CDATA[Didn't realize once again that waiting for a week to write this is such pain, I just took an earlier break to wait longer. *laughs* Ah hey, it was for something that has been bugging me for a while, so why not take a break and fix more of this blog while I'm at it, yes? *wink* Hehe alright don't try to be cute that indie game "Haven Park" you just finished(?) playing is cuter than you Speaking of cute, we have a real cutie up for the story today! I still am thinking of how to justify myself being able to own an abode in such an upscale neighbourhood though. Even if I own this, I still gotta pay for the maintenance, right? That has got to cost a lot. Yeah, fictional me is working just to pay for this. To whoever that doesn't want me to ditch this inheritance, I hate you- Oh, fictional me. *laughs* Oh, and keep this from the girlfriend, would ya? I haven't told her I am cohabiting with... well]]></description><link>https://knwebreports.onrender.com/posts/2024/03/the-fanfiction-20240323.html</link><pubDate>Sat, 23 Mar 2024 19:14:00 +0800</pubDate></item> <item><title>The Dream Fragment 20240319</title><description><![CDATA[<br>Okay before I forget and since I have some time before all hell breaks loose lol, let's talk about what happened last night! In my dreams, please, we don't do hostage situations in real life-<br>"I think I was in a covert operation to snatch someone from a public underground carpark surrounded by private apartments. On call, as the black cars stopped, we all went in to subdue all the people within, with me stepping in quickly to carry out Minase Inori, who has been held hostage a while ago.<br>I princess carry her out of the car, hiding into the row of parked cars behind, and this was when a set of reinforcements appeared as soon as everyone else in the group was taken out by them. I looked away in fear, wondering how to escape with a woman on my arms. I stayed down and crawled away swiftly towards my left. I saw the door to another private apartment and thought that if that were to be open and we can hide, it will fend us]]></description><link>https://knwebreports.onrender.com/posts/2024/03/the-dream-fragment-20240319.html</link><pubDate>Tue, 19 Mar 2024 09:40:00 +0800</pubDate></item> <item><title>The Entertainment News '24 Issue #11</title><description><![CDATA[It sure was hard to just go through the weekend while trying to fix this blog bit by bit because DAMN I only spent like what, last night and this morning doing it? Heck, at least I didn't forget this week has White Day and wrote that one fanfic and also unintentionally reveal the line-up for the rest of the month hehe you're welcome. Well, not like anyone cares anyways (lol), so welcome back to another week of Anime and music! The new season is upon us though, "Majou to Yajuu" will probably conclude a little later considering it took a break, but I'm not so let's keep up with the newest stuff! All the info and opinions I provide here are free. *wink*<!--SECTION BREAK--><blockquote class="tr_bq anime" id="KanaTen10"> <div style="text-align: center;"> <span class="head-prefix"><b>アニメ</b></span >&nbsp;<span style="font-size: large;" >Oro]]></description><link>https://knwebreports.onrender.com/posts/2024/03/the-entertainment-news-24-issue-11.html</link><pubDate>Sun, 17 Mar 2024 22:09:00 +0800</pubDate></item> <item><title>The Fanfiction 20240316</title><description><![CDATA[Among all the obstacles I had to overcome and I don't mean real life lol read the title again, but damn did I really want to bring forward all my stories in later episodes(?) for the season in place of this one, all because they did something to my life somehow... via the Internet. Damn am I sad this week is almost over, but I think I might just stick with what I have prepared for the week instead. I intend these to not be spoilers but heck, sorry <a href="https://www.instagram.com/reel/C4iK6LJvo3q/?utm_source=ig_web_copy_link" target="_blank" >Kanno Mai</a > and <a href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=UTLsbTVljgI" target="_blank" >Nagae Rika</a >, we can wait for our fictional encounters later this month. *giggles* For this week though, I did not forget about White Day then again it's not like I have anything else to offer besides my white pee- ANYWAYS haha it's not that, so just like every romance-like]]></description><link>https://knwebreports.onrender.com/posts/2024/03/the-fanfiction-20240316.html</link><pubDate>Sat, 16 Mar 2024 18:30:00 +0800</pubDate></item> <item><title>The Entertainment News '24 Issue #10</title><description><![CDATA[Wow, I've been busy on this blog, huh, me? *giggles* From dreams to new package to simping on <a href="https://jisho.org/search/imouto" target="_blank">imouto</a> to this? Yeah I'm living the life in my dream resort hotel I have no idea what I was doing there besides playing with women, what of it? *laughs* Well not really, you can read the posts earlier this week for more info, but I did spend a couple more days (let's not say just weekends lmao) creating a draft floor plan of what it looked like, probably half topped up with my own imagination because we know dream retention is worse than my own memory which only makes this less convincing so *shrugs* haha If that counts as playing a game lmao, then let's add music and animation into that list to show that I have a fulfilled entertainment life for the week! Hell yeah when's the last time I gave a shit about life fulfilment lol<b]]></description><link>https://knwebreports.onrender.com/posts/2024/03/the-entertainment-news-24-issue-10.html</link><pubDate>Sun, 10 Mar 2024 22:11:00 +0800</pubDate></item> <item><title>The Fanfiction 20240309</title><description><![CDATA[Man, what a day! I wondered to myself this morning whether I should do anything to improve my life in any way, and I gave up. *laughs* What better way to improve your life than to sleep it through, yes? I seriously need a break from real life though, even if I haven't been doing much. But we're NOT going to talk about real life here haha read the title again dear reader, because it's that time of the week where I am able to let all of life's responsibilities go and write about... well not Asakura Momo, we did her yesterday. *dabs* We are writing about your friend instead haha we are all fans of you here, that's for sure. *giggles* So <a href="https://jisho.org/search/39" target="_blank">thank you</a> Natsukawa Shiina for seriously awakening the <a href="https://jisho.org/search/oniichan" target="_blank">onii-chan</a> in me because this time around, we shall write about how this all started. Not real by the way, the real l]]></description><link>https://knwebreports.onrender.com/posts/2024/03/the-fanfiction-20240309.html</link><pubDate>Sat, 09 Mar 2024 19:07:00 +0800</pubDate></item> <item><title>The Klassic Note Review 2024.03</title><description><![CDATA[Looks like we are starting the 10th anniversary of officially reviewing fully reviewed music releases with a couple *wink* of singles *sob* to celebrate- Oh, it's March now? Welp February haha also Happy International Women's Day by the way I did not plan for this although we do have women to talk about here today- What, "Soko ni Naru" has a female in it she sings in the songs I'm about to review hehe *dabs* In the new month though, I can't believe we already have a next review coming in real soon as I plan to give miwa's new single so spoiler alert we are giving the middle finger to RyokuShaka's new single this week haha screw you we need better songs, but maybe ideal songs cannot be our target at this point even after all these years, honestly. Reasonably good singles will be good enough. So will be for miwa's single but heck, let's talk about what will kickstart the year of... hopefully more bite-sized music releases and]]></description><link>https://knwebreports.onrender.com/posts/2024/03/the-klassic-note-review-202403.html</link><pubDate>Fri, 08 Mar 2024 22:22:00 +0800</pubDate></item> <item><title>The Welfare Package March 2024</title><description><![CDATA[Oh damn, this was stuck in the letterbox for a day and I didn't even know?? Well at least it's safe. Oh it's small, it's real small. Like my- Anyways, welcome back if you have been waiting and I have been bragging about it and thinking of what to post to Bluesky but this will do lmao, we're back with another one of these... packages featuring a lot of Japanese female voice actress stuff just because I don't like anything else in this world. Oh, I also like Anime. And Japanese music. So yeah, I don't spend a lot. *laughs* Speaking of which, we do have 2 of the 3 things mentioned above right in this one, and I will do a separate review of the other ones not today because I want to listen to voice actress podcasts later just like the simp I am- I'm totally into this culture by the way, even if I know next to nothing. *giggles*Okay long enough intro, let's begin!]]></description><link>https://knwebreports.onrender.com/posts/2024/03/the-welfare-package-march-2024.html</link><pubDate>Thu, 07 Mar 2024 21:20:00 +0800</pubDate></item> <item><title>The Dream Fragments 20240306</title><description><![CDATA[Happy birthday Ede-chan by the way. Hope you don't mind me dreaming of not you despite the close distance phone wallpapers I've been putting of you for the week so far. *silence* And let's not talk about Sasaki Nao even though she would be an even better as my bride which is not what is in this context hehe<br>More dreams I can recall, this one's a lot more scattered though, but damn am I ever getting closer. To women. Haha- DAD WENT ARE YOU HERE THOUGH lol<br><br><br><br>"I was at a wedding of Kido Ibuki asking with my dad. All I could recall was my dad was selecting photos of the bride as they were giving it out for free. My dad then said to pay for them as if he were a simp or something, which made me want to say it too but I just did not have the courage to do it.<br>Another (disconnected) part of this is when my dad was looking at a (paper printed) list of top video games. My si]]></description><link>https://knwebreports.onrender.com/posts/2024/03/the-dream-fragments-20240306.html</link><pubDate>Wed, 06 Mar 2024 07:59:00 +0800</pubDate></item> <item><title></title><description><![CDATA[<b>Either our lives are under the decisions made by someone, or we make the decisions and ruin the lives of everyone else.</b><br>And that's why the world has to be evil. It's totally Darwinian, and hear me out. Even me not writing this part here is a good example that we cannot be good just to make everyone happy, we make very selfish choices that make us think we are evil, and we are. How do you think the homosapiens survived and had the smartest brains of all ape-kind? And now we are protecting all the idiots that were supposed to be killed long time ago through evolution? Pft, no wonder we are our own enemy.<br>P.S. I'm sure I wrote here in my personal space on the Internet instead of in Bluesky so I don't have to be evil and offend anyone out there. Think about it.]]></description><link>https://knwebreports.onrender.com/posts/2024/03/either-we-are-under-decisions-by.html</link><pubDate>Mon, 04 Mar 2024 21:31:00 +0800</pubDate></item> <item><title>The Dream Fragment 20240304</title><description><![CDATA[<br>Also is this is the first time I mixed virtual with reality? Well, not what you think but hear me out, yes?<br>"I was in a resort-like abode with a huge living area space facing the sea. I was holding a skimpy red sleepwear with black laces and I think I told to myself that this will look great on her, though I distinctively recall I also saw Ayane from DoA series around in a swimsuit, or maybe it was another person of the same name.<br>Regardless, I found Isobe Karin and she told me she is enjoying herself while wearing... I think what looks like a summer outfit? Let's say it's a dress of sorts. I told her to try this out, obviously with much reluctance from her. I said it's either she wears it now or tonight, and she took the sleepwear from me. I followed her to a corner of the living area space, and she put it on without taking anything off..."<br>Yeah, lame I guess, but somehow I can't forget how]]></description><link>https://knwebreports.onrender.com/posts/2024/03/the-dream-fragment-20240304.html</link><pubDate>Mon, 04 Mar 2024 07:52:00 +0800</pubDate></item> <item><title>The Entertainment News '24 Issue #09</title><description><![CDATA[You know how much it sucks to dream of Akarin but then not even be anywhere close to her? Why is my pee white though? *laughs* Oh wait maybe I should not use this for the intro LMAO now that I have regretted my life choices, hopefully I have not so in creating a Bluesky account, signed up for Tomita Miyu and Horie Yui fanclubs, AND wrote another fanfiction about Rieri?&nbsp;*silence* Let's not say it's too real but I may be posting on Bluesky more often than not, we may not need to write them statements here no more. We shall see about that. Same handler as my Twitter though, I changed that too. Anyhow, a less complicated week this week, hopefully I will get better after whatever trip to the doctor's (again) has done to my physical health... let's not talk about those and focus on Anime and music!! Yeah, I'm "only into Japanese anima]]></description><link>https://knwebreports.onrender.com/posts/2024/03/the-entertainment-news-24-issue-09.html</link><pubDate>Sun, 03 Mar 2024 22:14:00 +0800</pubDate></item> <item><title>The Fanfiction 20240302</title><description><![CDATA[New month, new story, I guess! I mentioned before this one will also be to celebrate another occasion and boy I have been coping with these feelings of love for her all this week, I feel like breaking it to her now that I have a girlfriend <i>miiiiight</i> be a bad idea after all.As such, we will delay the sadder story, for next time. *wink* I know right, there's that many people who want to be with me. Who am I, an <a href="https://jisho.org/search/ikemen" target="_blank">ikemen</a>- Oh, fictional me. *laughs* Hey, sorry for actually dreaming earlier that was a nice nap knowing that my coughing can be saved yet again lol, so let's properly daydream now. I gotta continue to show how cool I am to the girls, aren't I- Oh, fictional me. *laughs* If she isn't annoying enough here as she says she is, that's normal. She is infatuated towards me, naturally she will behave]]></description><link>https://knwebreports.onrender.com/posts/2024/03/the-fanfiction-20240302.html</link><pubDate>Sat, 02 Mar 2024 18:20:00 +0800</pubDate></item> <item><title></title><description><![CDATA[<b>Sometimes, just sometimes, I wonder if I've robbed someone of their dream for just being alive.</b><br>Watching back on Anime movie "JoseeTora" with Kumiko the main girl strapped onto a wheelchair, she has big dreams even though she's stuck at home most of the time. I wonder if for me being physically fit(?), among other things, that I've not done much compared to someone who isn't who will have bigger goals and dreams than me.<br>Maybe, just maybe that's why, I should be involved in charity more.]]></description><link>https://knwebreports.onrender.com/posts/2024/02/sometimes-just-sometimes-i-wonder-if.html</link><pubDate>Wed, 28 Feb 2024 22:27:00 +0800</pubDate></item> <item><title>The Entertainment News '24 Issue #08</title><description><![CDATA[Maybe I should mention her more even just talking about Anime in that Q&amp;A last year, but hey, happy birthday Hanazawa Kana!! I mean, how can you NOT know her at this point and how adorable this married woman is? *silence* I should just stop lol I mean I didn't even write Fanfiction of her this week- Also, it's as if "Majo to Yajuu" realized that the new "GREAT PRETENDER" series is dropping by and knew to skip a week of airing their new episode, we shall see them next month I guess. Meanwhile, maybe let's get back to that Confidence Man lore picking up where we left off. Yeah, pick up as in that old couple picked up Dorothy washed up on to <strike>Chinese</strike> Taiwanese shores or something instead of pronounced dead. But who knows, I only watched the trailer. *laughs* Another week of Anime and music, folks! The new package is coming soon, I promise. *wink*]]></description><link>https://knwebreports.onrender.com/posts/2024/02/the-entertainment-news-24-issue-08.html</link><pubDate>Sun, 25 Feb 2024 22:08:00 +0800</pubDate></item> <item><title>The Fanfiction 20240224</title><description><![CDATA[Well, it's a hot afternoon out here and my sinus is not in the mood to take a nap yet (lol), so why not do this first? *giggles* Unlike the weather now and boy how is staying inside an air-conditioned room worse, this week, in celebration of a birthday of a certain someone (which we will do another next week so FYI), we are introducing a new woman into my life! Well, in my fictional life, you know I can't get chicks. *silence* Anyways, this might be too intimate for my own good *giggles*, but also this might need more imagination as much as I have tried, and no, we are not talking about Kana-chan even though it's her birthday tomorrow. *dabs*You can figure it out, this week I will be talking about...!!<div class="separator" style="clear: both; text-align: center;"> <img alt="Kouno Marika in a thin blue top covered bel]]></description><link>https://knwebreports.onrender.com/posts/2024/02/the-fanfiction-20240224.html</link><pubDate>Sat, 24 Feb 2024 16:00:00 +0800</pubDate></item> <item><title>The Twenty-Second Book Worth of Photos: The Semi-Realistic Dream</title><description><![CDATA[Well, if it's a dream, might as well go full-on about it, yes? I won't go as far as that dream I had though, that might be too far even for this girl hehe I don't know if this counts as Valentine's Day gift or my birthday gift (to myself lol), but heck remember when I said a couple of years ago I don't even care about Ogura Yui? Guess that didn't age well. *laughs* And since my hesitation to make this arrive on the former occasion, I guess I shall spend my birthday *giggles* talking about a new photobook! This must be the most trippy thing I did in years since she isn't even in my list of favourite idols lol, but this can't be worse than real life so might as well!! *laughs* I didn't expect to ever give someone a photobook review outside of my own list of idols, but we are running out of firsts to give (lol), so maybe this is the year I actually walk out of my comfort zone.So let's!<]]></description><link>https://knwebreports.onrender.com/posts/2024/02/the-twenty-second-book-worth-of-photos.html</link><pubDate>Mon, 19 Feb 2024 16:20:00 +0800</pubDate></item> <item><title>The Entertainment News '24 Issue #07</title><description><![CDATA[I mean, I can wait until tomorrow to give myself the pat on the back for making it through another year. *laughs* Yeah, being old is ROUGH haha maybe it's time to set new goals for myself Still doing daily posts for the long weekend right here, of course I will not work tomorrow and boy is making myself a coding project smaller than my- such a great gift for myself, I don't think I need a photobook review. *silence* Haha who am I joking I just watched <a href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=VHdOu4OjnL0" target="_blank" >Ogura Yui's Valentine's Day livestream</a > (which is super late in timing, with respect) (no, I did not skip Koko-chan's radio for this ie. I missed half of that instead) and yeah, she is cute. I'm going to say it again tomorrow Yui-chan if you want to hear something else other than "you look like an elementary student" LMAO I didn't say that the fans did She did reve]]></description><link>https://knwebreports.onrender.com/posts/2024/02/the-entertainment-news-24-issue-07.html</link><pubDate>Sun, 18 Feb 2024 22:06:00 +0800</pubDate></item>
			</channel>
		</rss>